Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/michelle-j-b2b70b104 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Nursing

Patient Safety

Languages

English

Certifications

Crisis Prevention (CPI)

Registered Nurse (compact state licensure)

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support (ACLS)

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Michelle Jolly, BSN, RN

Registered Nurse †#

United States

Summary

Experienced Travel Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Management, Healthcare Management, Healthcare, and Patient Advocacy. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Nursing from Chamberlain University.

Experience

Local Hospitals and facilities in Arizona Travel and per diem Registered Nurse January 2018 - Present (2 years 6 months) Arizona

HEDIS, Quality Analyst Manager, Triage, Medical Surgical, Hospice and Behavioral Health.

Hospital Recovery Treatment Center Staff Registered Nurse January 2017 - Present (3 years 6 months) Arizona

Registered Nurse for both Adult and Adolescent unit with eating, behavioral disorders in areas that may include SH/SI, trauma, PTSD, substance abuse detox and recovery.

Multiple companies
Registered Nurse
July 2017 - Present (3 years)
Scottsdale, Arizona

(Per Diem RN-Independent Contractor)

Lead RN Corporate Health nurse for public, occupational health, health insurances for vaccinations: flu/TB/Hep series, biometrics, blood draws including quantiferion gold testing.

Private Duty Nurse

Independent Consultant RN July 2016 - December 2017 (1 year 6 months)

Scottsdale, Arizona

Independent Contractor for in home, private client nursing care.

Various companies for RN travel, per diem and on-staff. Registered Nurse 2016 - January 2017 (1 year)

Experiences include quality analyst manager, HEDIS abstractor, corporate/occupational/public health, triage, behavioral/psych, crisis-detox, urgent care. med surg, tele, hospice.

Procel Nurses & Allied Nurse Staffing Account Manager for Travel and Per Diem . January 2006 - November 2013 (7 years 11 months) Hermosa Beach, California

Supplemental Health Care

Nurse Staffing Account Manager for Travel and Per Diem.

October 2004 - December 2006 (2 years 3 months)

Otosurgical Group Medical Clnc
Back Office Medical Assistant Manager
June 1999 - October 2005 (6 years 5 months)
Century City

Education

Chamberlain University
Bachelor's Degree, Nursing · (2013 - 2016)